♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
SO, HONEY,
THIS, UH...
THIS THREESOME
THING, UH
I MEAN, HOW ARE WE EVEN GOING
TO START TO FIND...
ACTUALLY, I'VE BEEN MAKING
A LIST OF ALL THE WOMEN I KNOW
WHO MIGHT BE INTO DOING THIS.
OH. WOW.
HUH?
BOY.
WOW, SOMEONE'S BEEN
DOING THEIR HOMEWORK.
YEAH.
OH, AND I KNOW GAIL ROSTEN
IS IN THERE TWICE
BUT SHE IS SO...
OH, I KNOW.
YOU KNOW, JUST, JUST
TALKING ABOUT IT IS...
GETTING ME KIND OF...
I KNOW, ME, TOO.
YEAH?
WELL, I THINK
BEN'S ASLEEP.
OH, UM...
YOU KNOW, I THINK
IT'LL BE BETTER
IF WE JUST SAVE IT.
YEAH.
RIGHT. SAVE IT--
I CAN DO THAT.
( karate yell )
HEY, PHEEBS.
HEY.
HOW'S IT GOING?
WELL, I GOT TO GET
OUT OF THIS BED!
I'M GOING CRAZY HERE!
CRAZY!
HERE YOU GO, SWEETIE.
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS,
HERBAL TEA?
I HATE HERBAL TEA.
I PUT SOME HONEY IN IT.
( mockingly ):
NYI, NYI, HONEY IN IT.
SHE DOESN'T KNOW
SHE WAS FIRED YET, DOES SHE?
NO. THE DOCTORS SAY
IT MAY KILL HER.
WHAT ARE YOU TWO GIRLS
WHISPERING ABOUT OVER THERE?
BUT I THINK WE
SHOULD TELL HER.
I MEAN, IT'S JUST SO REALISTIC.
YEAH, I KNOW.
YEAH. HIS NAME'S PAT.
PAT THE DOG.
OH! OH! I GET IT!
( laughs )
OH, GO...
ARE YOU, UH, YOU...
READY FOR A REFILL?
OH, I PROBABLY SHOULDN'T.
SO I WILL!
OH... WOW.
IT'S LIKE IT'S RAINING.
PRETTY COOL, HUH?
BUT IF YOU'RE THINKING YOU
COULD PUT A FISH IN THERE
AND IT WOULDN'T GET SUCKED
UP INTO THE MECHANISM
WELL, YOU'D BE WRONG.
UM, CAN I USE YOUR BATHROOM?
IT'S, UH, RIGHT
THROUGH THERE.
OKAY.
( sighs )
YOU KNOW, I GOT TO TELL YOU
IF SOMEONE TOLD ME A WEEK AGO
THAT I WOULD BE PEEING
IN JOEY TRIBIANNI'S APARTMENT...
YEAH, LIFE'S PRETTY GREAT,
ISN'T IT?
I HOPE YOU'RE HUNGRY.
WE'RE STARTING
WITH OYSTERS.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY
SAY ABOUT OYSTERS,
DON'T YOU?
THEY HAVE PARASITES?
NO.
UM, WELL, SOME PEOPLE
SAY THAT OYSTERS ARE...
AN APHRODISIAC.
WHAT PEOPLE?
PEOPLE.
PEOPLE SAY IT.
COME HERE.
SO, OYSTERS, HUH?
( giggles )
AND THEN WE'RE
GOING TO HAVE
A LITTLE MIDDLE
EASTERN COUSCOUS.
SOMETHING WE CAN EAT
WITH OUR HANDS.
YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY
WHEN WE WERE STUDYING
COMMUNICABLE DISEASES...
NO, NO, NO, NO.
IT'S SENSUAL.
OH. DIDN'T KNOW.
OKAY.
( beeper sounding )
OH, NO!
I'M SORRY, SWEETIE,
IT'S THE HOSPITAL.
THAT FOOD LOOKS GREAT.
MAYBE SAVE ME SOME?
I CAN'T PROMISE ANYTHING.
WE'RE REALLY GOING
TO DO THIS, HUH?
LOOKS LIKE IT.
YOU KNOW, IF...
IF THIS IS TOO WEIRD FOR YOU
YOU CAN STILL BACK OUT,
ANYTIME...
( knocking on door )
I GOT IT.
OKAY.
SUSAN, HI.
HEY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR COMING.
I WOULDN'T HAVE MISSED
IT FOR THE WORLD.
I'M-I'M ROSS, BY THE WAY.
HELLO, ROSS.
I LOVE WHAT YOU'VE
DONE WITH THIS SPACE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
( both giggling )
HOW HOT IS THIS?!
I'M SORRY YOU'RE HERE
WITH ME
INSTEAD OF ROGER.
YEAH, ME, TOO.
WELL, I COULD MAKE IT SEEM LIKE
HE'S HERE.
HERE'S SOME LITTLE-KNOWN FACTS
ABOUT COUSCOUS:
THEY DIDN'T ADD THE SECOND COUS
UNTIL 1979.
( babbling )
STOP IT! THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
OKAY.
I'M SORRY, OKAY.
IT'S JUST, TONIGHT WAS
SUPPOSED TO BE, YOU KNOW...
WELL, IT WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE A BIG DEAL.
WHAT WAS TONIGHT?
YOU DON'T WANT TO KNOW
WHAT TONIGHT WAS.
OKAY.
WHAT WAS TONIGHT?
WELL, TONIGHT WAS...
WAS GOING TO BE MY FIRST TIME.
WITH ROGER?
NOT JUST WITH ROGER?
OH, MY GOD!
ALL RIGHT, RELAX,
MR. I'VE-HAD-SEX-FOUR-TIMES!
FOUR DIFFERENT WOMEN.
I'VE HAD SEX WAY MORE TIMES.
HOW MANY?
NINE.
I WAS WAITING FOR
THE PERFECT GUY,
YOU KNOW.
WELL, GOOD.
GOOD FOR YOU.
YOU REALLY THINK
THAT ROGER IS THE PERFECT GUY?
NO. HE'S NOT A HORRIBLE GUY.
HEY, THAT'S WHAT I TELL GIRLS
ABOUT ME.
CHANDLER, I'M GOING TO DIE
A VIRGIN!
NO, YOU ARE NOT.
YOU ARE SWEET AND WONDERFUL
AND THIS IS GOING TO HAPPEN
FOR YOU.
REALLY? WHEN?
YOU WANT TO DO IT WITH ME?
OKAY.
I WAS KIDDING.
SO WAS I.
JOEY...
YOU'RE SUCH AN AMAZING ACTOR.
HOW DO YOU KNOW WHERE
DR. DRAKE RAMORAY LEAVES OFF
AND JOEY TRIBIANNI BEGINS?
WELL, WITH DR. DRAKE
THEY ALWAYS TELL ME WHAT TO SAY.
AND WITH JOEY, I PRETTY MUCH
HAVE TO MAKE IT UP ON MY OWN.
WOW.
HMM.
TELL ME SOMETHING, JOEY...
WHOA!
OH.
I JUST FELL RIGHT OFF
THE COUCH THERE.
YEAH, YOU DID.
I'M OKAY.
OKAY, HERE YOU GO.
WHOOPS.
LET ME ASK YOU
A QUESTION.
YEAH?
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
SOMEONE TOLD YOU
JUST HOW BEAUTIFUL
YOU ARE?
WOW.
I CAN'T...
I CAN'T FEEL MY HANDS.
OH, WELL, COME HERE.
HMM?
HUH?
OH?
( retching )
WE CAN'T DO THIS.
NO.
( laughing )
OYSTER?
YEAH.
OKAY, NOW, IF, IF,
IF WE DID DO THIS
THERE'D BE A LOT OF PRESSURE
ON ME, YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE YOU'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR A VERY LONG TIME
AND I WOULDN'T WANT
TO DISAPPOINT YOU.
YEAH, BUT SEE, I HAVE NOTHING
TO COMPARE IT TO.
SO EVEN IF YOU WERE HORRIBLE,
HOW WOULD I KNOW?
I DO LIKE THAT.
IT'S HARDER FOR ME--
I'VE GOT THOSE FOUR OTHER WOMEN
TO COMPETE WITH.
WELL, IF IT HELPS,
THERE WERE ONLY THREE.
SO, IT WOULD JUST BE
FOR TONIGHT, RIGHT?
ABSOLUTELY.
IT WOULD JUST BE ONE FRIEND
HELPING OUT ANOTHER FRIEND.
STOP IT. WE'RE NOT DOING THIS.
LET'S DO IT.
NO. OKAY!
OKAY!
SO, UM...
DO YOU HAVE ANY,
UH, MOVES?
I HAVE SOME MOVES.
I HAVE NO MOVES.
OKAY.
OKAY, WHAT YOU
DOING THERE?!
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M SORRY, THIS IS
JUST TOO WEIRD.
YEAH, LET'S
JUST FORGET IT.
YEAH. WHAT IF I TURN OUT
THE LIGHTS?
OKAY.
Chandler:
OH, YEAH.
CHANDLER?
( passionately ):
YEAH?
THAT'S THE COUCH.
OH, MY GOD.
I KNOW!
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING--
WE ARE GOING
TO DO THAT AGAIN.
OH, OKAY!
( laughs )
MORNING.
OH, RIGHT.
YEAH.
OH, GOD.
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE
JOEY TRIBBIANI
HEARD ME THROW UP.
YEAH, I MEAN, HE ACTUALLY
SAW YOU A LITTLE BIT, TOO.
NO.
OH, GOD, WE... HEY, WE...
WE DIDN'T, UM...
NO, NO. NO.
NOT AFTER SEEING THAT.
GOD, I'M JUST A HORRIBLE PERSON.
WHY?
BECAUSE I'M MARRIED.
THAT'S RIGHT--
I'M A MARRIED WOMAN
AND I CAME TO A
TV STAR'S APARTMENT
TO HAVE AN AFFAIR. UGH!
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
I'M NOT A "STAR."
I'M JUST A REGULAR FAMOUS ACTOR.
YEAH, AND I'M A HORRIBLE,
HORRIBLE PERSON.
RACHEL, WILL YOU
STOP SAYING THAT?
HEY, HEY, LOOK...
REMEMBER ON THE SHOW
WHEN CAPRI WAS DYING
AND SHE GAVE ME...
THE RING FROM
THE CAVE, YEAH.
WOW. UH...
OKAY, WELL... UH...
( gasps )
OH, MY GOD!
THEY LET YOU KEEP
THAT STUFF?
SURE. AS LONG AS
THEY DON'T FIND OUT
YOU CAN KEEP
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
AND I WANT YOU TO HAVE IT.
NO, NO, NO, I COULDN'T.
YES, YES.
AND EVERY TIME YOU LOOK AT IT
I WANT YOU TO REMEMBER
THAT YOU... ARE A GOOD PERSON.
OKAY, NOW, YOU HAD
THE CHANCE TO CHEAT--
AND... WITH ME--
BUT YOU DIDN'T
AND THAT'S WHAT
THIS RING STANDS FOR.
BUT I THOUGHT THAT RING
STOOD FOR CAPRI'S
UNDYING LOVE HER BROTHER.
YOU WANT THE RING OR NOT?
YEAH.
HEY, YOU'RE UP.
ALL RIGHT.
LOOK AT YOU.
THOUGHT I'D TRY
TO TAKE A WALK.
WILL YOU POUR ME
SOME WATER?
I'LL BE BACK SOON.
WHOA. YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO USE THE PAY PHONE
TO CALL WORK, ARE YOU?
NO. I'VE LEARNED
MY LESSON.
OKAY.
THANKS.
LET'S GO.
COME ON, MOVE IT.
MOVE IT, PHOEBE, COME ON.
SHOES, BRIEFCASE.
THANKS, LOU. GOOD LUCK
WITH THE GALLBLADDER.
HEY, JOEY, DID...
DID YOU EVER HAVE
A THREESOME?
UH... UH...
LOOK, ROSS, I THINK
CAROL'S GREAT
AND I'M SURE YOU'RE
A VERY ATTRACTIVE MAN
BUT I...
NO.
NO, THE REASON I'M
ASKING IS THAT...
( laughs )
I SORT OF HAD ONE
LAST NIGHT.
YOU?
YEAH.
WOW.
ALL RIGHT, SO...
WAS IT AMAZING?
IT WAS... IT WAS...
OKAY.
JUST OKAY? DID YOU DO IT RIGHT?
LOOK, IT'S JUST...
DID YOU EVER GO TO A PARTY
AND THINK "WOULD ANYONE REALLY
MISS ME IF I WEREN'T HERE?"
HUH.
BUT STILL, ROSS...
YOUR WORST DAY WITH TWO WOMEN
IS PRETTY MUCH BETTER
THAN ANY OTHER DAY.
OH, OH, NO, ABSOLUTELY.
( both laughing )
YEAH.
IT'S JUST...
MY PART SEEMED TO BE
OVER PRETTY QUICKLY
AND THEN... AND THEN...
THERE WAS A LOT
OF WAITING AROUND.
OH.
BUT YOU GOT TO BE
WITH BOTH OF THEM, RIGHT?
NOT-NOT REALLY.
IT WAS JUST CAROL.
NOT THE OTHER ONE?
NO, SHE KEPT
KICKING ME AWAY.
OH. YEAH,
YOU DON'T WANT THAT.
NO.
NO. WELL, HEY, AT LEAST
YOU GOT TO SEE A LOT OF STUFF.
OH, I SAW A LOT
OF STUFF.
YEAH.
YOU GET A LITTLE BORED?
A LITTLE.
YEAH. MADE A SNACK.
YEAH? WHAT...
WHAT'D YOU HAVE?
JUST A SANDWICH. YEAH.
TURKEY...
A LITTLE MUSTARD.
SOUNDS GOOD.
IT REALLY WAS.
HEY.
LET ME TELL YOU ABOUT THIS CHICK
I SCORED WITH LAST NIGHT.
OH, NO, WAIT A MINUTE--
THAT WAS YOU.
HEY, CHECK ME OUT.
I'M A SLUT!
SO YOU WANT TO DO SOMETHING
TONIGHT?
OH, I CAN'T--
DR. ROGER'S COMING OVER AGAIN.
OH.
OH, RIGHT, RIGHT,
BECAUSE YOU'RE STILL SEEING HIM
AND, UH, HE'S A GOOD GUY.
I MEAN, I REMEMBER A TIME...
( snoring )
ARE YOU OKAY?
( chuckling ):
YEAH. TOTALLY.
TOTALLY. ARE YOU?
GREAT. IT'S SO AMAZING.
I MEAN, LAST TIME
DR. ROGER CAME OVER
I WAS SO NERVOUS
BUT THEN AFTER BEING WITH YOU
I'M ALL, LIKE,
"CAN THE DOCTOR SEE ME NOW?"
I'LL BET HE CAN.
"YOU KNOW, I DON'T HAVE
AN APPOINTMENT
BUT I SURE COULD USE
A PHYSICAL."
( chuckling )
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY?
OH, YEAH. DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME--
I'LL BE FINE.
( karate yell )
( gasps ):
OH!
MY GOD... BARRY!
Y-YOU SAID YOU WERE GOING
TO BE AWAY ALL WEEKEND.
OH. THAT'S RIGHT.
I'M SORRY. I AM EARLY.
FINISH, PLEASE!
SURPRISE. LOOK WHO'S BACK.
HEY, PHEEBS.
HEY.
CALL SECURITY.
PHEEBS, UH,
DIDN'T YOU GET FIRED?
I DON'T THINK SO.
PHOEBE?
JACK! HEY.
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
ALL BETTER. BACK TO WORK.
EXCEPT THIS CLOWN FROM RESEARCH
TOLD ME I WAS FIRED.
HE SHOULD DO HIS
RESEARCH, HUH?
WELL, YOU WERE FIRED.
NUH-UH.
I TOLD THAT GUY
WHO ANSWERED YOUR PHONE.
OH. OKAY,
I DIDN'T GET THAT MESSAGE
SO THIS DOESN'T COUNT.
ANYWAY, I'LL BE IN MY OFFICE.
UH, PHOEBE, I... YOU-YOU
DON'T HAVE AN OFFICE.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT--
I'LL-I'LL WORK RIGHT HERE.
THIS IS GOOD.
NEXT TO THIS PLANT.
PHOEBE, LET'S NOT
MAKE A SCENE.
YOU'RE IN MY OFFICE.
LOOK...
I HAVE MADE A LOT OF CASH
FOR THIS COMPANY, OKAY?
I AM TALKING BIG BUCKS--
PESOS, YEN, RUBLES.
YOU MAKE ONE LITTLE MISTAKE...
YOU LOST $13 MILLION.
OH, SO NOW THIS IS
ALL ABOUT MONEY?
YOU KNOW
IT'S BAD ENOUGH THAT... OW.
OH, YOU HAVE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M HAVING ANOTHER
HEART ATTACK.
WHAT?
I'M HAVING ANOTHER HEART ATTACK!
CALL 9-1-1!
TAKE IT EASY, NOW.
DUMB-ASS!
HEY, PHEEBS.
HOW'S IT GOING?
THEY FIRED ME
AND I'M HAVING A HEART ATTACK.
OH. WELL,
WELCOME BACK.
YEAH.
HI, ROSS.
HI, RACHEL.
IS JOEY TRIBIANNI HERE?
UM... NO.
WELL, IF YOU SEE HIM
WILL YOU PLEASE TELL HIM
THAT I'M LOOKING FOR HIM
AND THAT THIS TIME, I AM
NOT GOING TO THROW UP!
ARE YOU OKAY?
ME? I'M GREAT.
I'M FINE. I'M SO GOOD.
BUT... YOU KNOW
WHO'S NOT GREAT?
MEN.
YOU'RE A MAN, RIGHT, ROSS?
YEAH.
SIT DOWN.
OKAY.
LET ME, UH...
LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
DO WEDDING VOWS MEAN SQUAT
TO YOU PEOPLE?
AND WHY IS IT THAT
THE SECOND WE TELL YOU
WE ARE GOING OUT OF TOWN,
BAM, THERE YOU ARE IN BED
WITH THE NEIGHBOR'S DOG-WALKER?!
WE'RE SORRY.
NO, SERIOUSLY. SERIOUSLY.
WHAT HAS HAPPENED
TO THE SANCTITY OF MARRIAGE?
DIDN'T YOU SPEND
LAST NIGHT AT JOEY'S?
OH, WHAT ARE YOU, A DETECTIVE?
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING
ON WITH YOU AND YOUR HUSBAND
AND WHAT IS HOPEFULLY
AN ADULT DOG-WALKER...
LOOK, CAN I JUST SAY
NOT ALL MEN ARE LIKE THAT.
OH...
HEY...
THERE ARE SOME MEN
WHO WILL DO
WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO MAKE THEIR
MARRIAGE WORK.
'KAY, THERE ARE SOME MEN
WHO WILL STAND BY AND
WATCH AS THEIR WIVES
ENGAGE IN WHAT CAN ONLY BE
DESCRIBED AS A TWOSOME...
WITH-WITH SOME WOMAN SHE
BARELY KNOWS FROM THE GYM.
WHO ARE THESE MEN?
JUST-JUST MEN.
A GUY I KNOW.
WELL, YOU MIGHT
WANT TO TELL HIM
IT SOUNDS LIKE
HIS WIFE... IS GAY.
SHE IS NOT...
SHE'S GAY.
OH, MY GOD.
SHE IS SO GAY!
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
GOOD DAY FOR MARRIED
PEOPLE, HUH?
I'M SORRY YOUR HUSBAND
CHEATED ON YOU.
I'M SORRY YOUR WIFE IS GAY.
I GUESS WOMEN AREN'T
THAT GREAT, EITHER, HUH?
TRY TELLING MY WIFE THAT.
OKAY TO COME IN?
YEAH, COME IN, EAT,
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
DR. ROGER GOT BEEPED AGAIN.
YEAH, I KNOW.
GUESS WHO BEEPED HIM.
WHAT?
I'M THE RUPTURED SPLEEN.
( laughs )
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
BECAUSE YOU SHOULDN'T
BE WITH HIM.
YOU...
YOU SHOULD BE WITH ME.
REALLY?
YEAH. WHEN YOU WERE
TALKING ABOUT ROGER
THAT WAS KILLING ME. LOOK...
THINGS LIKE LAST NIGHT
THEY DON'T JUST HAPPEN,
YOU KNOW
OR AT LEAST NOT TO ME.
AND WITH THE OTHER TWO WOMEN...
IN THE MORNING, YOU KNOW,
I WOULD JUST LIE THERE
AND I COULDN'T WAIT TO JUST
GO HANG OUT WITH MY FRIENDS
BUT WITH YOU...
I WAS, YOU KNOW,
ALREADY WITH A FRIEND.
CHANDLER...
I KNOW YOU PROBABLY DON'T WANT
TO GO OUT WITH ME, YOU KNOW
'CAUSE I MAKE TOO MANY JOKES
AND I'VE NEVER BEEN
IN A SERIOUS RELATIONSHIP
AND I GUESS I'M NOT
TECHNICALLY A "DOCTOR."
THERE WAS JUST ONE
WOMAN, WASN'T THERE?
NO, THERE WERE TWO.
INCLUDING ME?
OH, YEAH.
♪ IT ONLY TAKES
TWO HEART ATTACKS ♪
♪ TO FINALLY MAKE YOU SEE ♪
♪ ONE OF THEM WON'T DO IT ♪
♪ BUT THE SECOND'LL
SET YOU FREE ♪
♪ TELL ALL YOUR HATE AND ANGER ♪
♪ IT'S TIME TO SAY GOOD-BYE ♪
♪ AND THAT IS JUST
WHAT I WILL DO ♪
♪ SOON AS THOSE BASTARDS
I WORKED FOR DIE... ♪
Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]